[Forging Justice]
[Episode 15]
Come on.
Come on in.
This is our office.
And here is your seat.
My wife sewed that cushion for you,
meaning to keep you warm,
since you're a female comrade.
Goji berries,
a local specialty here.
When you steep them in water,
add a few pieces of rock sugar.
The taste is good.
They also benefit the stomach.
Thanks, Mentor.
But don't you worry about me.
I'm actually quite tough.
Really?
Alright.
Let's go check out the dorm.
Sure.
Okay.
Come with me.
Here.
Come this way.
Mentor.
Is the prison break real?
Don't scare yourself.
It's pretty safe here.
Prison break?
There hasn't been one such incident here.
Look at this place.
Can escapees possibly get away?
This is the dorm.
But usually nobody lives in there.
You see, the downtown
is 50 kilometers away.
There are shuttle buses for commuting.
After work,
staffers would rather take the bus home
and return early the next morning.
Oh right.
This is the restroom.
Look,
here.
It's a public restroom.
Remember,
take a flashlight with you
when you go at night,
so you won't fall,
as this is a dry toilet.
Besides,
that's the washroom.
Feel free to do your washing
right there.
Be careful with this.
Try not to let the oil drip on you.
It doesn't wash off easily.
Please come in.
You'll stay here.
I've got you some hot water.
My room is right next door.
If you need help,
just knock on the wall
like this.
I'll try not to.
It's okay.
Alright. Sort your things out
and get some rest.
If you need anything,
just let me know.
Thank you, Mentor.
Forgo the formality.
Is it heavy?
I can manage.
Mom, let me take it.
Mom.
Let's just go.
Go.
Yu,
are your family visiting?
A co-worker of mine.
Hello, Mr. Yu, Mrs. Yu.
Hello.
I'll leave you to it.
This is it, my room.
Here it is.
Come on.
Give it to me, Mom.
Come on in.
Here, Mom.
Have a seat.
Dad, sit down too.
Gaoyuan.
Is this your uniform?
Yes.
I wear it to court.
Mom, have some water.
Are you tired?
No, not at all.
We sat on these two bags all the way here.
It was cozy.
Didn't I ask you to buy sleeper tickets?
Why standing tickets instead?
Did I not send home enough money?
You did. It was enough.
Sleeper tickets are hard to buy.
Why the hassle?
Plus, it's not easy for you
to make money here.
Put it on now.
I'd like to see you in it.
I'm not wearing it in here.
Just put it on.
It's too hot in here.
Mom, talk to him.
I want to see you in it. Put it on.
Now!
Be good and do it.
Fine. I'll put it on.
Help me with it, Dad.
Look, my love.
Our boy is successful now.
I'm taking it off. It's too hot.
You had us hurry over.
Is there a matter?
Dad, take a seat.
I mean to let you meet some people.
What people?
I'm dating someone
with a view to marriage.
So I asked you
to come meet her and her family.
[Binjiang Intermediate People's Court]
The car's not here yet.
Going out to work?
Director Ma.
Yu.
Yes?
You seeing someone?
Who told you that?
Many people saw you and Fang Haohao
at the municipal government
family compound.
The girl
with a bad leg, right?
She was once
an intern here.
Listen,
have confidence in yourself.
People say that she's out of your league,
but I'd say it's unfair to you.
Out of my league? How so?
Yeah. That's so not true.
I think it's you who's too good for her.
You're an outstanding young lad,
aren't you?
Ignore her.
What a gossipy snob.
She's just
the canteen purchasing director,
yet she acts as if she's a real leader.
Wait,
what did she mean by that?
Just an insinuation
about Fang Haohao's father.
What's with her father?
You don't know?
Drop the act already.
Just tell me.
Her father is a high-ranking official,
the deputy commander of a military region,
named Fang Leiming.
What's wrong with your kid?
Yeah. What is it with him?
Our shop has been open
for only a few days.
Right.
Such
ill-bred scum.
Excuse me.
Let me through.
Officer, you be the judge.
Chief Zhang.
We devoted our lives to this shop.
What's going on?
The same old strife.
It just keeps on and on.
Look at that.
It's Sun Rong's eldest son's doing.
He poured kerosene in broad daylight
and set the place on fire.
I don't even dare to imagine.
See, the shop's surrounded
by houses.
If the fire had spread,
many people would've died.
Right.
Sun Rong insisted that we call you,
saying that he knows you
and you have authority.
I told him it was
no use asking you to come over,
but he wouldn't listen.
He's over there.
Got it. I'll go take a look.
Okay.
Sun.
Prosecutor Chen!
Prosecutor Chen,
you must help me.
You must help me.
Get up.
My son...
My son is not even 14 years old yet.
Nothing bad should happen to him.
Why didn't you keep watch on him?
I tried, but I failed.
My son...
did that out of hatred.
I heard Wang Youxi's shop was burned
soon after it reopened. Is it true?
Yes, Sun Rong's son did it.
What the Wangs did to that child
really left a mark in his heart,
don't you think?
Wang Youxi and his wife must be
sentenced harshly.
Where does that come from?
The harm caused
by Wang Youxi to Sun Rong's family
is not a one-time thing.
The influence continues.
Even to this day,
Sun Rong's family are still being hurt
psychologically
and in their daily lives.
What about the Wangs?
Their shop reopened
and they started a new life.
What should they have
gone for, if not a new life?
Is starting a new life
equal to another crime?
They should've taken a proper attitude,
admitted their guilt,
felt some remorse,
and offered compensation, right?
But what have they done now?
Not only have they done none of that,
but they also don't think they are wrong.
Isn't reopening the shop
a way to earn money
so they can compensate the Suns?
Mentor, if...
if you put it that way...
You think I'm trying to
smooth things over, right?
If Wang Youxi and his wife are not
given a severe sentence,
Sun Rong's family
will lose faith
in judicial justice.
From here on out,
they won't believe in the law anymore.
Besides, now, Sun's son is not
even 14 years old yet.
What if he goes down the path
of crime?
His whole life will be ruined, right?
Wang Youxi's child is only 8 years old.
Yes. And the Wang family
drove the Sun family crazy.
The former was not even mistreated.
The trial is the day after tomorrow.
Have you decided
to still suggest
the court give a harsher sentence?
Yes, I've decided.
The maximum sentence
for hooliganism is
only 7 years of imprisonment.
It's too easy on the Wangs.
How long do you think is appropriate?
Ten years.
Even if the number goes up to 15,
it'll still serve them right.
Didn't we agree
not to meet at each other's workplace?
Why? Afraid of people talking?
No, just the inconvenience of coming out.
What's up?
You look upset.
Bring these to your father.
Didn't we make a pact?
You're supposed to bring them
to tonight's dinner.
Why are you giving them to me now?
I'll bail on it.
Yu Gaoyuan, what are you trying to say?
Just spill it.
Your father
is Fang Leiming, right?
Yes. Is there a problem?
He's a regional military commander.
A deputy one.
What difference does it make?
Yeah.
Does it make
any difference to you
whether he is
a breeder or a military commander?
I didn't mean to hide it from you.
It wouldn't be necessary or possible.
I just wanted us
to get off
on a simple start.
If you think I handled it poorly,
then I apologize to you.
So you did have concerns, right?
Right.
I did.
I just... I just feared that...
Well, I overthought things.
I just doubted
if you approached me
and pretended to like me
because of my father's status.
What? Just because I'm from a rural place,
I'm not good enough for you?
No, it's me.
Because of my leg, I feel inferior
and I'm sensitive and suspicious.
It is I who is not good enough for you.
Okay?
You're a judge who graduated from
a prestigious university
and you excel in every way.
Would you possibly fall in love with me?
Forget it.
You're proud,
and I feel inferior.
Our relationship was only a coincidence.
I was thinking too much.
Let go. People are watching.
Then let them.
It hurts.
It really hurts.
You're pressing on my ear.
Let me ask you.
What exactly do you like about me?
Your leg.
Is it because I look like
that girl you went to collage with?
You're not like anyone.
Fang Haohao,
I'm 27 years old now.
I was in a relationship
that failed badly.
I handled some major problems
in a terrible way,
and hence lost many friends.
Everything I said that day
when I first met you
is true.
None of it is a lie.
I like you for no other reason...
than just you.
Take these back.
Don't be late tonight.
This is it.
Oh right.
I have a stepmother
who is not much older than us.
She likes stirring up trouble.
If she acts up later,
just ignore her.
Why do you always spring surprises on me?
Saying it sooner or later is all the same.
You're here to meet
my father, not her.
Let's go.
Let me carry that stuff.
Tidy up my clothes, please.
Fix them.
You look fine.
I'm a bit nervous.
Let's go.
Carry you on my back?
No need.
Let's do.
No need at all!
Come on in now.
They're waiting.
Welcome home!
Come on. Take a seat in here.
Let me take your things.
Dad,
this is Yu Gaoyuan.
He works at
the Municipal Intermediate People's Court.
Hello, Mr. Fang.
Go have a seat.
I've heard many good things about you
from Haohao.
She has rarely praised anyone
ever since she's a kid.
Zhang,
bring some slippers over.
No need for those.
My dad tracks mud everywhere
anyway when he finishes gardening.
Mr. Fang,
Haohao specifically
told me to buy these.
Previously, I took
a trip to Beijing
and bought these pastries for you.
He can't eat too much of these,
due to his high blood sugar.
Zhang!
Coming!
Hurry.
What a handsome young man.
It's a blessing for Haohao
that you are attracted to her.
It's also a blessing for you.
Pressure, too.
Yes.
Haohao
is no ordinary girl.
You have to tame her,
or you'll suffer.
Am I right, Fang?
Eat some more.
Haohao...
has been good at poetry,
calligraphy, and painting
since she was this tall.
She always got the first place
in speech contests,
math contests,
language competitions, and whatsoever.
She excels in everything!
Isn't that right, Haohao?
It's a pity that she has a permanently
damaged leg.
What a shame.
God must be jealous of her.
God has no mercy.
Mr. Fang, easy on the drinks.
Have some more food.
Just call me Fang!
Why put a "mister" before it?
You'll be calling me Dad in the future.
He's right.
Easy on the drinks.
What now?
Are you looking for trouble?
Go get me the pastries.
My daughter had them bought for me.
I want to eat them now!
Haohao got in this condition
when she was in kindergarten.
Her real mom passed away early.
She suffered this because of me.
It was all my fault!
You did nothing wrong.
I just had bad luck.
How stubborn.
She takes that after her mom.
Haohao has a sharp tongue
but a soft heart.
She specifically asked me
to buy those pastries for you
from Daoxiangcun's head store
on Dongsi Street.
She even made a list
of what you enjoy
eating.
I almost missed
the train for that.
Yu.
I've seen plenty of
young men like you.
Having humble origins. Calculating.
Smart. Aiming high.
Puffed with ambitions,
and very realistic.
But it doesn't matter!
You managed to quickly
win my daughter's heart over.
That was no easy feat.
You're quite an outstanding young lad.
That said,
I don't care about your motives,
or if you truly
love my daughter.
Just you remember, young lad,
to treat my daughter well,
even if you have to fake it.
Otherwise, I will
hunt you down one day.
Did you hear me?
I heard you.
I'll give it my all to make her
happy.
Eat, Mr. Fang.
Sure. Sure.
You'd hate
to come to my home again, right?
Not just you, even I don't
want to be back here again.
Your father really loves you.
It's understandable that he lectured me.
He didn't do that out of love.
He just couldn't wait
to get rid of me.
Then his life will be much easier.
It's always been like this
since I was little.
I've grown used to it.
In this world,
one can still live well alone.
I don't need a home,
nor do I expect anyone to love me.
Alright, don't be upset.
Let's change the subject.
When I get off work tomorrow,
let's meet up.
Why?
I'd like you to meet my parents.
It's unnecessary.
How so? It is necessary.
I don't need your pity.
Who's pitying you? I'm begging you.
Begging me for what?
For your hand in marriage.
What's in it for you?
What's in it for me?
Let me think about it.
I aim to marry up,
to suck up to Commander Fang,
and to score a successful career.
You happy now?
It's settled then.
Let's meet my parents tomorrow
and get married on Monday.
You're back.
Why are you still up, Dad?
With things on my mind,
how can I fall sleep?
What's on your mind?
Only when I saw with my own eyes
your abode in Binjiang
and the clothes you wear
did I finally believe
that my son really grew up
and became an official.
I'm not an official yet.
How are my brother and sister
doing at home?
They're doing fine.
When I get better off in a few more years,
I'll have you all move here.
The year you took
the college entrance exam,
I burned joss paper
at the ancestral graves,
praying to our ancestors
for helping a descendant of ours
to succeed.
Who would have thought?
After graduating from college,
my son was assigned to this little town.
At the thought of you
getting married here
and probably being tied down
right here for the test of your life,
I'm upset.
When we eat, we take one bite at a time.
When we walk, we take one step at a time.
Go to sleep, Dad.
Time to tuck in.
The inmates here
are all felons, most of which
are on death row with reprieve
or life imprisonment.
When a prisoner is transferred here,
his original household registration
will be revoked
and moved to Bieshan, namely here.
This causes
strong resistance among the inmates
and increases the difficulty
of management.
Guys,
there's a girl here!
The more you fear,
the more they enjoy it.
-Hey, girl!
-Hey, lady!
Hey, girl!
Look here!
Young lady!
Girl, look at me!
Hey, girl.
You have a really slim waist.
Song Changhe,
do you want to throw away the points
you've collected this month?
Don't do that, Prosecutor Guo.
W-We're just giving her
a warm welcome, aren't we?
-Welcome!
Apologize to Prosecutor Zhang!
Look at him, so mad.
Prosecutor Zhang,
my apologies.
-She's coming over!
-She is!
You're Song Changhe, right?
You had better behave.
I'll remember you.
She'll remember you!
-She said she'd remember you!
-Listen to that!
My apologies,
Prosecutor Zhang.
Speak up!
I can't hear you!
-She's feisty.
-So tough.
My apologies,
Prosecutor Zhang!
You just caved like that?
He caved!
You chicken!
Now,
the prosecutor will
read the indictment.
Honorable Presiding Judge, Judge,
and People's Assessors,
now,
appointed by and on behalf
of the Binjiang Municipal
People's Procuratorate,
I am initiating a public prosecution
against a hooligan gang
of four, including Wang Youxi
and Liang Yuemin.
The trial will proceed
under my supervision.
You said you didn't commit the murder.
Any proof?
I didn't kill,
and I have to provide proof of it?
Of course.
The procuratorate has plenty of evidence
to prove you did the murder.
They are holding
all the trump cards.
What do you have?
Besides,
only now are you saying you didn't kill.
W-Why did you admit guilt earlier?
Because they...
Cut it out.
Listen,
take my advice.
Don't fight it.
Prioritize your life.
When you get to court,
actively plead guilty, show remorse,
and beg for a lenient sentence.
Don't irritate the judge.
Strive for a death sentence with reprieve.
There will be
a trial of second instance, right?
Try to claim your innocence then.
As for me,
I'll collect more evidence
to your advantage.
What if I'm really sentenced to death?
What do you think I can do?
You might as well fire me now.
Their actions
not only inflicted severe trauma
on the victims,
but also undermined
the national law, humanity,
and moraliity.
I, as the prosecutor,
hereby specifically point out
that the defendants in this case
have shown no recognition
of their crimes to date
and have refused
to admit their guilt.
The defendants' behavior
is a blatant challenge
to the fundamental bounds
of the law and morality
honored by our society.
They must be severely punished.
Therefore,
the prosecution strongly suggests
that in accordance to
Article 1 of the Decision
on Severely Punishing
the Criminals Constituting
Grave Damage
on Public Security, which was approved
by the standing committed
of the National People's Congress
on September 2, 1983,
the defendants in this case should be
sentenced above
the statutory maximum penalty.
Harsh punishments will serve them right!
Bravo!
-Well said!
-Bravo!
They deserve severe sentences!
What were they thinking
when they beat others up?
Bravo!
Order in the court!
The hearing is now concluded.
Sentencing will be announced
at a later date.
Adjourned!
Mentor!
Anything wrong?
We discussed
the submission
for sentencing.
You agreed with it.
Right, I did say the case
would be yours to handle
and decide.
Then why are you like this?
Are you regretting it?
Do you know
that what you just said
will stir up public hostility
towards the defendants?
But everything I said is true.
Is that so?
Yes.
Do you really think it that way?
Mr. Tan.
Hello.
My surname is Xia.
I'm the associate judge
for this case.
Nice to meet you.
I'm here to submit
the representation papers
and the defense statement.
So this is the defense statement?
Anything wrong?
The defendant
in this case might be
given a death sentence.
Please don't worry.
I've educated my client.
He will refrain
from talking nonsense in court,
actively admit his guilt,
receive punishment,
and sincerely
apologize to the victim's family,
so as to strive for a lighter sentence.
How are you going to fight
for a lighter sentence for him?
The defendant had a conflict
with the victim
due to family issues.
They should have
resolved the problems properly
through consultation,
guided by correct values.
However, the defendant
failed to properly settle family disputes.
Harboring evil intents,
he killed and dismembered the victim,
displaying utterly grave
subjective malice.
The defendant employed
exceptionally cruel means.
The circumstances of his offense
were especially egregious,
resulting in
extraordinarily grave social impact.
The defendant in this case
deprived another of life
and dismembered the body with cruel means.
His actions
constitute the crime
of intentional homicide.
He merits
the maximum penalty of law.
Defendant,
do you plead guilty to the crimes
you are charged with
in the indictment?
I am innocent.
Presiding Judge, I really am innocent!
I didn't kill her.
Okay.
The court notes your opinion.
Defender,
what is your defense?
The indictment consists of
clear facts of the crimes
and conclusive evidence.
I, as the defender, have no objections.
However, the defense
would like to point out
that the killing in this case
happened in the heat of passion
triggered by escalated family conflicts.
So its danger to the society
is relatively small.
Regarding the cause of the incident,
it cannot be said
the victim was entirely without fault.
As a wife, she allowed
a third party to intrude
into her marriage,
pressured the defendant for a divorce,
and refused to return to the defendant
the bride price he paid
to marry her,
hence causing constant tension
in their relationship.
For that, the defendant
fell into a state of despair.
The defendant always behaved well
and abided by the law.
This is his first offense
and an isolated incident.
After his arrest,
he truthfully confessed to his crimes
with a cooperative attitude.
Therefore,
the defense believes
that the defendant should be
given a lighter sentence.
I deny the charges!
I didn't kill my wife!
Don't you gang up
to frame me.
And you said the defendant admitted guilt
with a cooperative attitude?
I really am innocent!
Why don't you believe me?
Defendant, calm down.
Let me ask you.
When was the first time
you admitted guilt?
I can't recall.
They told me
they'd let me sleep
as long as I owned up to it.
They made me stay awake for days.
Why did you refuse to admit guilt
in several prior interviews?
Xia,
why did you ask that?
I didn't kill my wife.
What guilt was there to admit?
What was there to confess?
I didn't know a thing!
There are five confessions here.
They were all stated by you.
In each of them, the time,
the place,
the murder weapon,
and the killing method
are different.
Why?
They instructed me to say all that.
You keep referring to "they."
Who do you mean?
Xia.
Defense counsel,
any response
to the questions I asked?
Do you have anything to say?
No.
Xia Yingjie,
what on earth did you mean by that?
Mei,
as the trial proceeds, I'm finding
more and more doubts.
I still suggest we return the file and ask
the procuratorate to investigate again.
Didn't we have an agreement?
Why are you asking
to return the file again?
Do you think you are being fair?
Just now, in the court,
you were clearly steering
the defense counsel.
You are totally biased!
Fine.
I admit
it's true
that some interview records
provided by the police
lack compliance.
But this is
a sensational case in the whole city.
How can the basic facts
be denied for just a few records
that fail to meet the standards?
One of the basic facts is
that we cannot confirm
the deceased was Yu Sanhua,
Qian Xingliang's wife.
So you firmly believe Qian Xingliang
is not the murderer, right?
Then when you get out later, just announce
that he is innocent and is free to walk!
He might or might not be
the murderer.
That's why I only suggested
we return the file
for supplementary investigation.
Keep rationalizing it!
Xia.
I'm sorry.
I might have been
a little emotional just now.
Mei.
I understand every word you said.
You understand all that.
Then why do you
still have to be this stubborn?
Because I don't want blood on my hands.
And is there blood on my hands?
Xia,
could you relent
just this once for my sake?
Mei,
this has nothing to do with that.
The matter is not between us.
Fine then.
The collegial panel
failed to reach a consensus.
Let's report it
to the Adjudication Committee.
Three, two, one.
Fix yourselves up
before we take another photo.
Okay.
Gaoyuan.
Put on your uniform for a photo.
No, I'm not wearing it.
You already brought it. Why say no?
Put it on.
Fine.
I'll take a picture with you two.
Haohao, have a break.
I'll take a photo with them.
Okay.
The three of you take a family photo.
I'll stay out of it.
Haohao.
Our family is poor.
We don't have much to offer.
When I married into the family,
Gaoyuan's grandmother
gave this ring to me.
Now, it can
finally be passed down.
Take it.
No, you should keep it.
Customs are changing now.
This is not a tradition anymore.
Just keep it, Auntie.
Still calling me Auntie?
You won't call me Mom
until after the wedding.
Right?
No need for any changes, Mom.
Haohao isn't used to calling anyone Mom.
Just let her call you Auntie.
So this is what
a high-ranking official's child is like.
You declined the ring
or to call me Mom.
Mom.
I'll take the ring.
I'll take it.
Good, very good.
Put it on.
Now, the whole family is happy.
How wonderful.
Put it on. This is great.
Mom, sit down.
Gaoyuan.
Are we being impolite?
What do you mean?
Does Commander Fang
not know
that we are in Binjiang now?
The two of you only invited us here
to take photos.
It's okay.
My dad really doesn't know,
since I haven't told him yet.
But... marriage is a big deal.
I thought...
Please don't worry.
I make decisions about my own life.
About him, too.
Just don't worry. Mom.
Come on.
No more talking. Time for photos.
Get ready.
Smile.
Please get closer.
Look at the camera.
This is good.
Three, two, one!
Here, Mom.
Wash your feet.
Anything wrong, Mom?
Sit down.
This is so unfair to you, my good boy.
How is it unfair to me?
Look at that girl.
You even have to marry into her family.
It is our fault for being impoverished.
I know you're trying
to climb up the social ladder.
If you had been allowed to stay in Beijing
back then, you could've found
a better girl.
Mom, what are you talking about?
She and I chose each other.
Besides, her father is a military officer.
I'm not a soldier.
What can he help me with?
Then what do you see in her?
That girl
is not easy to deal with.
I like it that she teases me
and has me wrapped around her finger.
My goodness!
Did your father
give you your name
and work his tail off
to support you through college
so you could be
a servant to someone?
Is that what you think?
I was just joking.
Let's drop the subject.
Don't be mad.
I'm telling you,
once she marries you, she'll be
the Yu family's daughter-in-law.
I don't care if you get on top
of her or the other way around.
Just make sure you won't be
a disgrace to the Yu family.
Tame her, or I won't
acknowledge you as my son anymore.
Alright, Dad.
Don't be mad.
Dad, stop being mad.
You two get some rest. I'm heading out.
Talk some sense into him.
[Adjudication Committee Conference Room]
This is a significant case.
The whole city and even the province
are breathing down our necks.
Yet the collegial panel
failed to reach a consensus.
How did that happen?
I think the prosecution has basically
listed clear facts
and conclusive evidence.
By law, the accused, Qian Xingliang,
should be sentenced to death.
But Xia Yingjie disagrees.
In my opinion, there are
substantial doubts in this case.
Even the identity of the deceased
cannot be absolutely confirmed.
It is irresponsible to rush
to a verdict.
Although the deceased has been identified
through blood typing
and her relatives' identification,
neither of these is conclusive.
A skull superimposition test
has been done as well, right?
Right.
But a person's identity
cannot be established
unless the 64 indicators
in all the 4 categories
of the said test produce a complete match.
If inconsistency is found
in two or more indicators,
then the identity cannot be confirmed.
What's the problem now?
Negative match in two indicators.
Didn't you just say
the criterion was inconsistency
in more than two indicators?
I said two or more than two.
It's not a 100% match.
No case is 100% certain.
Another thing is,
the defendant's confessions
show a process of gradually
aligning with the facts.
I suspect he was subjected to inducement.
Your suspicion isn't equal to the truth.
Besides, there is other proof.
That kitchen knife counts, right?
But there are still doubts.
This murder weapon was not
recovered until over 10 days
passed after the incident.
Yu Sanhua's blood
was surprisingly still on it.
It's logically questionable.
Anything else to add?
Court Pres. Jiang,
I...
would like to criticize myself first.
Why rush for that?
The two of you
please step out.
We need to deliberate on this.
Court Pres. Jiang,
members of the committee,
I have a few remarks to add.
If we let a murderer walk
for now, there is still
a chance to remedy it in the future.
But if we take a man's life
for the wrong reason...
Save that emotional speech.
Please leave the room now.
Mei, I'm sorry.
Alright, say no more.
Maybe I'm right,
or maybe you are.
But it doesn't matter now.
How do you think
the committee will rule on this?
Court Pres. Jiang gave
clear hints, didn't he?
A death sentence, absolutely.
I already told you
this is a wild goose chase.
Now, even I am dragged into this mess.
What if...
I mean, hypothetically,
what if giving Qian a death sentence
turns out to be a mistake?
Xia,
if you're worried about
taking responsibility for it,
I can tell you for sure
that we will be
both to blame.
Neither of us will be off the hook.